David Dilanchian

- david.dilanchian@pm.me
- https://davidldilanchian.info

(514) 515-2845

Objective

Experienced Contractor with a demonstrated history of working in the computer and network security industry. Skilled in Negotiation, Analytical Skills, Microsoft Office, Fintech, OS Development, Product Knowledge, and Management. Strong professional & entrepreneurship studied at Université de Montréal.

Experience

Co-Founder at HayFinTech

January 2017 - Present

• Research, design, develop, and test blockchain technologies • Maintain and extend current client- and server-side applications responsible for integration and business logic • Be involved in the global blockchain community—work on implementing and integrating the latest improvement proposals

Web Analyst at Show Viral

December 2015 - Present

 Produce reports for the Management team
Plan, develop and manage web and mobile campaign and channel tracking
Collaborate with sales and marketing teams

Manager & Owner at Cafe Babylonia

April 2013 - December 2015

My Coffee Shop • Manage day-to-day operations of the coffee shop • Hire & Train Employees • Nurture friendly relationships with customers to increase loyalty

Sales Representative at Action 500 Paintball & Karting

March 2012 - April 2013

Promote & sell products and services while exceeding sales forecasts Establish, develop and maintain positive business and customer relationships Analyze the territory/market's potential, track sales and status reports

Sales Representative at SAIL Outdoor Equipment

Store

March 2011 - April 2012

Educate customers on how products or services can benefit them financially & professionally Maintaining positive business relationships to ensure future sales Supply management with reports on customer needs, problems, interests, competitive activities, and potential for new products

Grill Master at Harvey's

April 2007 - December 2011

Trained and managed a team of 3 prep-cooks and achieved significant improvements in their productivity. Monitoring consistently the food quality and service quality of orders being served. Successfully handled opening and closing of establishment.

Projects

SCAMA

https://github.com/david-dilan/SCAMA

Teaching Senior Citizens how to start and use Computers/Social Media/Internet - Windows 10 / iOS / Android - Gmail / YouTube / Google

Scouts Leader at Homenetmen Montreal

https://www.homenetmenmontreal.com

Scout Leaders are primarily responsible for organizing the activities of the group, and training the youth members through the Scout program. - Leadership - Liaison with Parents/Districts

Laval Electoral Campaign 2017

https://www.laval.ca/

Electoral Campaign Volunteer during the 2017 Laval municipal election - Market the candidate - Participated in door-to-door canvassing events

Skills

Programming	Microsoft Office: Word /	Languages: English -C2
Languages: Python / C++	Excel / PowerPoint /	(Proficient) French -C2
/ nodeJS / Typscript	Access / Publisher /	(Proficient) Armenian -
HTML5 / Bootstrap 4 /	MyAnalytics / Visio /	B1(Intermediate)
Angular 2	SharePoint	

Education

Vanier College

DEC in Social Science

September 2009 - May 2012

Saint-Maxime

DES Concentrations Science

September 2006 - June 2009